Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 1; 13.6 cubic ft.
  - Meeting Materials [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1977 September 16-1977 September 17 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1977 September 16-1977 September 17 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 January-1978 June (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 June 03 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 July 08 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 August 13 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 September 15-1978 September 16 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 October 14 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 November 18 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 December 09 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 January 19-1979 January 20 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 February 24 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 March 17 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 April 07 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 April 29 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 May 18-1979 May 19 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 June 16 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 June 16 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 July-1979 August (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 September 14-1979 September 15 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 October 20-1979 October 21 (Box 12 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 November 17 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 December 08 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 January 12-1980 January 13 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 February 09 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 March 08 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 April 12 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 April 12 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1978 May 05-1978 May 06 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 May 17 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 May 17 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 May 17 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 June 07 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 July 12 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 13 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Meetings, Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - NYSARC v. Carey, US Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit Nas. 80-7289, 80-1295, Review Panel Salaries and Expenditures [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Operational Plans [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Reports to the Court [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Reports to the Court [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Reports to the Court [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Staff Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Staff Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Staff Reports, Fenton, John V. [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Weekly Work Schedule [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 14 (1-Administrative Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
- Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 2; 2.0 cubic ft.
  The Review Panel issued formal recommendations to New York State on the implementation of the Willowbrook Consent Decree. If the State chose not to accept the recommendation, the matter was decided by the U.S. District Court judge assigned to the Willowbrook case.
  This series contains correspondence, reports, and court documents related to the Review Panel's formal recommendations. Each recommendation has its own folder, and folders are arranged chronologically by recommendation date. The first 22 recommendations issued by the Panel were numbered in the original filing scheme, but subsequent recommendations were not. The second box contains an index, written in late 1978, for recommendations 1-22, including a summary and outcome for each recommendation. Selected files are restricted because they contain information about specific named residents of Willowbrook and other state developmental centers. These restricted folders are noted below in the box and folder list.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Formal Recommendations, Follow-up Status and Responsibility [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Formal Recommendations #1, Transfers and Placements [RESTRICTED], 1975 October 06 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Formal Recommendations #2, Keener Services Center [RESTRICTED], 1975 October 06 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Formal Recommendations #3, Access to Records/Use of Restraints [RESTRICTED], 1975 October 07 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Formal Recommendations #4, Education [RESTRICTED], 1975 October 14 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Formal Recommendations #5, Behavior Modification [RESTRICTED], 1975 December 23 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Formal Recommendations #6, Equal Compensation [RESTRICTED], 1975 December 24 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Formal Recommendations #7, Panel Staff/Administrative Assistant [RESTRICTED], 1976 January 27 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Formal Recommendations #8, Psychiatric Unit [RESTRICTED], 1976 January 27 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Formal Recommendations #9, Second Access to Records [RESTRICTED], 1976 January 28 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Formal Recommendations #10, Medical Services [RESTRICTED], 1976 February 11 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Formal Recommendations #11, Reinstatement of Residents to Education Program [RESTRICTED], 1976 February 24 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12-13)
  - Formal Recommendations #12, Clothing [RESTRICTED], 1976 February 19 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Formal Recommendations #13, Class Membership [RESTRICTED], 1976 June 11 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Formal Recommendations #14, Removal of Class members from Hillcrest Unit, Wassaic Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1976 August 19 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Formal Recommendations #15, Request for Defendants to Join Panel in Requesting Amendment of the Consent Judgment [RESTRICTED], 1976 November 30 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Formal Recommendations #16, Community Placement Plan Sections V (6) and V (7) [RESTRICTED], 1980 April 14 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Formal Recommendations #17, Bronx Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 March 11 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19-22)
  - Formal Recommendations #18, Consultants to Train Trainers [RESTRICTED], 1977 March 21 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Formal Recommendations #19, Evacuation of Gouverneur Residents [RESTRICTED], 1977 August 30 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Formal Recommendations #20, Consumer Advisory Board Staffing [RESTRICTED], 1977 September 13 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25-26)
  - Formal Recommendations #21, Deputy Director for Management and Training Director Positions [RESTRICTED], 1977 December 03 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Formal Recommendations #22, Definition of 'Children' [RESTRICTED], 1978 May 02 (Box 1 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28-29)
  - Formal Recommendations #22, Definition of 'Children' [RESTRICTED], 1978 May 02 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1-4)
  - Index to Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1978; Undated (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Formal Recommendations Flower Fifth Avenue Hospital Admissions [RESTRICTED], 1979 May 24 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Formal Recommendations Panel Budget [RESTRICTED], 1979 June 27 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Formal Recommendations Community Placement [RESTRICTED], 1979 August 22 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8-9)
  - Formal Recommendations Community Placement Audit Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1979 August 22 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10-14)
  - Formal Recommendations, Responses [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15-16)
  - Formal Recommendations, Case Management Staffing [RESTRICTED], 1980 March 17 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17-18)
  - Formal Recommendations Upstate Community Placements [RESTRICTED], 1980 March 18 (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Additional Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (2-Formal Recommendations [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
- Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 3; 19.3 cubic ft.
  The Willowbrook Review Panel conducted numerous audits of Willowbrook and other state facilities housing former Willowbrook residents to determine levels of compliance with the terms of the Consent Decree. This series contains data, reports, correspondence, and other materials related to Review Panel audits. Please note that Community Placement Audits are found not in this series, but in the Community Placement series (Series 6).
  Review Panel auditors closely examined the records of selected facility residents as part of the audit process. The series is restricted because it contains medical and educational records of specific named residents of Willowbrook and other state developmental centers.
  Arrangement varies by subseries.
  - Willowbrook Audits [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 3.1; 5 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains files on audits conducted at Willowbrook (later renamed Staten Island Developmental Center). Included are audits of buildings at Willowbrook managed by United Cerebral Palsy. Files are arranged chronologically by audit date, then alphabetically. Audits found in this series include Willowbrook Core Audits I-IV (1976-1977), the Willowbrook Joint Audit of 1977, the Willowbrook Audits of July 1977 and February 1979, the United Cerebral Palsy Audits of November 1977 and November 1979, and the Educational Reinstatement Audits of February and April 1977.
    Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically.
    - Surveys, Dental Clinic [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Surveys, Dining Room Conditions [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Surveys, Food Service and Nutrition [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Surveys, Policy and Procedure Manual [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Surveys, New Personal Service Items [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Surveys, Deficiencies and Plans of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Compliance Audit, Willowbrook Task Force [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Developmental Plan Audit [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit, Client Sample List [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit, Data Sheets, Originals [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit, Developmental Plan Formats [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit, Technical Assistance Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit I, Background [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit I, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit I, Report [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit I, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit II, Background [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit II, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit II, Notes [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit II, Recreation [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit II, Report, First Draft [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit III, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit III, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit III, Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit I-III, Comparison [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Core Audit IV, Plans [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Living Conditions and Environment, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Programming Draft [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Recommendations, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, Staffing, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
    - Willowbrook Joint Audit, January 1977, Program Definitions [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Compliance Audit, January 1977, Report [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, February 1977, Background Materials [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, February 1977, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, February 1977, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Developmental Plan Audit [RESTRICTED], 1977 March (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, April 1977, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, April 1977, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, April 1977, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Education Reinstatement Audit, Final Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Auditor Data Sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Auditor Summary Sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 5 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 7 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 8 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 8 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 13 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 15 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 15 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 20 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 32 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 76 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 76 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data, Building 77 [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Data Staffing [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Recommendations, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Report [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Willowbrook Audit, July 1977, Technical Assistance Unit [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
    - Willowbrook Audits [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1977 November (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Data Sheets, Nina Eaton Center [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Data Sheets, Nina Eaton Center [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Data Summary [RESTRICTED] (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Data Summary [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Data Summaries and Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, November 1977, Nina Eaton Center [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Willowbrook Audits [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Willowbrook Audit, Client Sample Configurations [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Willowbrook Audit, Medical Services Information [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Master Data Summaries [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Physical Environment [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Willowbrook Audit, February 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit [RESTRICTED], 1978 April (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, April 1978, Master Data Summaries [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, April 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, April 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Audit, April 1978, Raw Data [RESTRICTED] (Box 3 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)